**2024-10-23 15:50 UTC Apologies for yesterday’s connection issue, which was resolved in 30 mins.**  
We’ve refunded all fees collected yesterday to advertisers and waived our fees for the next 24 hours to boost publishers' earnings

[Advertise](javascript:void(0))

Create

* [
    
    Banner ad campaign  
    Target your audience worldwide](https://a-ads.com/campaigns/new/)
    
    [
    
    Content Publication order  
    Choose from different ad formats](https://a-ads.com/marketplace/)
    
    [
    
    Affiliate program  
    Pay for useful actions with CPA model](https://a-ads.com/crypto-affiliate-program/)

Learn about

* [Advertising with AADS  
    Ad technologies for your promotion](https://a-ads.com/advertise/)
    
    [Catalog of Banner Ad Units  
    Choose from 1000s of websites](https://a-ads.com/catalog)
    
    [Ad Formats  
    Discover available banner formats](https://a-ads.com/ad-formats/)
    
* [Content Ad publication  
    Place ad at a fixed price](https://a-ads.com/marketplace/advertiser/)
    
    [Catalog of Publication offers  
    Publish ad in a few simple steps](https://a-ads.com/marketplace/)
    
    [CPA advertising campaigns  
    Reward publishers for targeted actions](https://a-ads.com/crypto-affiliate-program/)

[Earn](javascript:void(0))

Create

* [
    
    Banner Ad Unit  
    Embed simple code in a few clicks](https://a-ads.com/ad_units/new)
    
    [
    
    Content publication offer  
    Allow to place ad in your media](https://a-ads.com/marketplace/become_publisher/)

Learn about

* [Banner ad traffic monetization  
    Earn crypto on your website traffic](https://a-ads.com/earn/)
    
    [Earning from ad placement  
    Get more paying advertisers](https://a-ads.com/marketplace/publisher/)
    
    [AADS Referral program  
    Attract advertisers to AADS for a fee](https://a-ads.com/crypto-referral-program/)

[Advertise](javascript:void(0))

* Create
    
    [
    
    Banner ad campaign  
    Target your audience worldwide](https://a-ads.com/campaigns/new/)
* [
    
    Content Publication order  
    Choose from different ad formats](https://a-ads.com/marketplace/)
* [
    
    Affiliate program  
    Pay for useful actions with CPA model](https://a-ads.com/crypto-affiliate-program/)
* Learn about
    
    [Advertising with AADS  
    Ad technologies for your promotion](https://a-ads.com/advertise/)
* [Catalog of Banner Ad Units  
    Choose from 1000s of websites](https://a-ads.com/catalog)
* [Ad Formats  
    Discover available banner formats](https://a-ads.com/ad-formats/)
* [Content Ad publication  
    Place ad at a fixed price](https://a-ads.com/marketplace/advertiser/)
* [Catalog of Publication offers  
    Publish ad in a few simple steps](https://a-ads.com/marketplace/)
* [CPA advertising campaigns  
    Reward publishers for targeted actions](https://a-ads.com/crypto-affiliate-program/)

[Earn](javascript:void(0))

* Create
    
    [
    
    Banner Ad Unit  
    Embed simple code in a few clicks](https://a-ads.com/ad_units/new)
* [
    
    Content publication offer  
    Allow to place ad in your media](https://a-ads.com/marketplace/become_publisher/)
* Learn about
    
    [Banner ad traffic monetization  
    Earn crypto on your website traffic](https://a-ads.com/earn/)
* [Earning from ad placement  
    Get more paying advertisers](https://a-ads.com/marketplace/publisher/)
* [AADS Referral program  
    Attract advertisers to AADS for a fee](https://a-ads.com/crypto-referral-program/)

Privacy Policy
==============

**AADS is a bitcoin advertising network that respects your privacy.**

This Privacy Policy ("Policy") describes how AADS.com ("A-ads.com" or "AADS" or "we" or "our" or "us") collects, stores, shares, and uses information and your choices about privacy when you use our website, products and services (collectively, "Services"). If you see an undefined term in this Privacy Policy, it has the exact definition as in our Terms and Conditions [https://aads.com/terms\_of\_service](https://aads.com/terms_of_service). Your privacy is important to us, and we ask that you read this Policy carefully to be informed about our practices.

This Policy is part of our T&Cs. Any capitalized terms used but not defined in this Policy have the same meaning in our Terms and Conditions ("T&Cs"). By accessing or using our Services in any way, you agree that your information may be collected, stored, shared, and used as described in this Policy and our Terms and Conditions. By submitting any Personal Information through our site or by using our Services, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and expressly consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of your Personal Information by this Policy. The use and disclosure of your Personal Information by this Policy is essential to the proper functioning of AADS and our provision of Services to you.

WHEN THIS PRIVACY POLICY APPLIES
--------------------------------

This Policy applies to all of our Services, regardless of how you use them and whether or not you register for an AADS account. This Policy applies to how we collect, store, share, and use information. This Policy does not apply to any entity we do not own or control or to any person we do not employ or manage. If you are directed to a third-party site at any time while using our Services, you understand and agree that the third-party site's policies govern.

TYPES OF INFORMATION WE PROCESS
-------------------------------

Information You Provide: We may collect the information that you provide (such as your username, e-mail address, public cryptocurrency wallet address, and your social media profile, if any) or otherwise make it available to us when you access or use our Services, including when we need:

To identify you as a User in our system;

To provide our Services to you, including new Services we may develop later (reason: legitimate business purpose and/or performance of a contract);

To provide you with customer support (reason: legitimate business purpose);

To facilitate your communications or transactions with us (reason: to receive consent and for legitimate business purposes):

To operate, improve, and customize our Services, Content, and marketing, to develop new Services, and to understand how you use and interact with our Services and Content and the products, services, and Content of others (reason: legitimate business purpose);

To develop and display more customized Content and ads to you on or off our Services (reason: to receive consent and for legitimate business purposes);

To promote and maintain a trusted, safer, and more reliable environment on our Services, for example, to help detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, conduct investigations or risk assessments, or verify actions taken by you or associated with your account (reason: to protect our platform and its users and for legitimate business purpose);

To contact you (by e-mail or as otherwise authorized by you) to address issues with your account or use of our Services, collect fees, process payments, send payments, settle account balances, send you updates about your account, send you updates about our Services or policies, or for other purposes permitted by law (reason: performance of a contract and for legitimate business purpose);

To contact you (by e-mail or as otherwise authorized by you) to send you marketing communications, promotional messages, and offers about our Services and Content and the products, services, and Content of others (see below for information on how to opt-out of receiving certain communications from us) (reason: to obtain consent and for legitimate business purpose);

To facilitate your participation in contests, sweepstakes, or other promotional events sponsored or conducted by us or by others in conjunction with us (reason: performance of a contract);

To comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, or enforce our T&Cs or any other AADS policies or agreements with Users (reason: compliance with a legal obligation); and to perform different functions as described when the information is collected or requested, or for other purposes with your prior consent (reason: legitimate business purpose).

COMMUNICATION PREFERENCES
-------------------------

We provide registered Users with settings on our Services to control whether they receive certain communications from us. Suppose you do not want to receive a marketing e-mail from us. In that case, you can unsubscribe by following the unsubscribe link in the e-mail you received, changing your preferences in your profile and account settings (if you have registered for an AADS account), or contacting us via [https://aads.com/contact\_us](https://aads.com/contact_us). You may not be able to opt-out of receiving communications from us, such as e-mails about your account, your relationship with us, or your transactions with us or other Users. For further information, please don't hesitate to contact us via [https://aads.com/contact\_us](https://aads.com/contact_us). Please note that unsubscribing from receiving marketing e-mails from us may result in a less robust experience of our Services.

ACCOUNTS AND USER PROFILES
--------------------------

Registration, Access, and Records
---------------------------------

To register for an AADS account, you may be asked to provide your username, valid e-mail address, social network profile, cryptocurrency wallet address, and/or other data. If you have received our permission to use our Services as a business, you may need to complete an additional registration process and provide further information. If you have an AADS account, you may access, add, remove, or update certain information about you in your profile and account settings, as indicated on our Services. You are responsible for updating all such information as necessary to keep it accurate and current. When you update your account or profile information, we may keep a record of the unrevised information for purposes consistent with this Policy. If you wish to cancel your account, you may use the tools provided in your profile and account settings ([https://aads.com/user/deletion/new](https://aads.com/user/deletion/new)), subject to any other agreements between you and us and any transactions which have not yet been completed. If you terminate your account, we may keep a record of any or all information associated with you or your account, as required or permitted by law, for purposes consistent with this Policy. Any such data shall be attached to a unique identifier that cannot be used to identify you; specific account data that includes Personal Information, including your name, e-mail, contact information, and certain other records such as settings and collector profiles will be removed at such termination. For further information, please get in touch with us via [https://aads.com/contact\_us](https://aads.com/contact_us).

Profile and Account Information
-------------------------------

To make our Services more interactive, certain information about Users' profiles or accounts, including non-financial data relating to the performance of the advertisements you create or publish, may be made accessible to other Users on or through our Services, as indicated in Users' profile and account settings on our Services, or as otherwise indicated by us when you use certain Services. This information may include settings to control how particular profile or account information is shared with other Users on or through our Services. You should regularly check your profile and account settings to be informed of your current choices.

Data Retention: We will keep and use your data as described in this Policy for (i) as long as your account is in use, is open, or is active; (ii) as long as it is necessary to comply with any tax, legal, and/or other regulatory requirements; and (iii) to protect and defend against potential legal claims. If you would like to request the deletion of your personally identifiable information or request that it be returned to you, please get in touch with us via [https://aads.com/contact\_us](https://aads.com/contact_us).

By deleting your data from our site, you understand that you will no longer be able to use our Services. We will retain your anonymized, aggregated, depersonalized data after it has been deleted from our site.

FAVOURITES AND FOLLOWS
----------------------

Our Services may include features that enable you to designate your choice of topics, sectors, interests, categories, or other items. If you enable such designations, we may include you in e-mail communications regarding those designations. If you would like to opt-out of receiving those e-mails, please follow the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the relevant e-mail or visit your account profile to update your e-mail settings.

USER CONTENT
------------

As described in our T&Cs, some Services may enable you to provide User Materials on or through our Services. When you post or publish User Materials on our Services, any information in the User Materials (including information in images or videos) becomes publicly accessible on our Services (and may also be indexed by and accessible through third-party search engines). Other Users and we may access and use the User Materials as described in our T&Cs. This applies even if you or someone else also provides such information to us by other means. Our use of such information might have been more limited under this Policy if such information was only provided to us by other means. It is your responsibility to ensure that you have the right to share any information about others that you may share with us or with others through our Services.

USER COMMUNICATIONS
-------------------

Connecting with Publishers: We aim to provide a platform where Users can discover and engage with a wide range of Publishers worldwide. Advertisers may target ad units upon applying to use the AADS services.

Sharing Information with Other Users: currently, AADS.com does not facilitate communication between users via the AADS platform. However, some information is available publicly, such as the statistics of specific campaigns and ad units.

TO WHOM DO WE SHARE PERSONAL INFORMATION?
-----------------------------------------

Personal Information. Under this Policy, "Personal Information" means information that by itself can be used to identify or contact a specific person (for example, username, e-mail address, and/or your public cryptocurrency wallet address), and Personal Information does not include information that has been aggregated or made anonymous so that by itself it no longer identifies and can no longer reasonably be used to contact a specific person. In certain circumstances, Personal Information may also include information you voluntarily provide to us. We will not share your Personal Information with others other than in the ways described in this Policy or otherwise without your prior consent. In addition to the other sharing of Personal Information described in this Policy, we may share your Personal Information with others in the following contexts.

Service Providers: We may contract with third-party service providers that help us provide our Services or perform services for us related to them. They may process your Personal Information as necessary to perform those functions for us. Examples may include but are not limited to: identity verification, document authentication, public database review, payment processing, bill collection, fraud investigation, e-mail, and postal mail administration, customer service assistance, web and mobile data analytics, display ads, and server and database hosting services. To avoid doubt, we do not sell your Personal Information to our Service Providers.

Transactions: We may use third-party cryptocurrency wallet extensions to conduct cryptocurrency transactions. The applicable privacy policies govern your interactions with third-party cryptocurrency wallet extensions.

For conducting certain cryptocurrency transactions, we use third-party cryptocurrency payment processors such as Coinpayments.net; your interactions with Coinpayments.net are governed by [Coinpayments.net privacy policy](https://www.coinpayments.net/help-privacy).

If there are any errors you may make when using third-party cryptocurrency payment processors (such as sending the wrong cryptocurrency to a specific cryptocurrency standard wallet address), we may communicate directly with third-party cryptocurrency payment processors to ensure we receive your payment. You hereby authorize us to communicate with third-party cryptocurrency payment processors to solve any cryptocurrency payment errors on your behalf.

Business Transfers: If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of assets, your Personal Information may be one of the assets transferred. In this event, we will inform the AADS Users about a change of ownership of their Personal Information by updating this document or announcing it on the AADS website or through the AADS social media channels.

Legal Purposes: We may access, preserve, and disclose your Personal Information and/or other information if we believe that such access, preservation, or disclosure is reasonably necessary to: (i) comply with any law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request (such as search warrants, subpoenas or court orders), which may include responding to legal requests; (ii) enforce our T&Cs or our other policies or agreements with Users, or investigate potential violations; (iii) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; (iv) protect or enforce the rights or property of AADS, you, or any other person or entity; or (v) prevent physical harm to any person, including situations involving possible violence or self-harm.

AGGREGATED AND NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION
---------------------------------------

We may aggregate and/or make anonymous any Personal Information that we have obtained in any way from or about you or others so that such information no longer contains any Personal Information. We may use and share any aggregated, anonymous, or other non-personally identifying information for any legitimate business purposes, including research and development, marketing, and to inform others about how our Services or Content are engaged with or used.

OTHER WEBSITES AND SERVICES
---------------------------

Our Services may include links to other websites or services we do not own or control, and other websites or services that we do not own or control may contain links to our Services. Our Services may also include features that enable you to link your AADS account to your account on other social media services. For example, you may be able to sign up for (or sign in to) our Services through another social media service. Our Services may also include features that enable you to share Content on other websites and social media services. However, these links and features are not an endorsement by us of any other websites or services or any of their privacy policies or practices. When you visit or use other websites or services, they may collect information from you, including through the use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of other websites and services that you visit or use to be informed of their practices.

INTERNATIONAL PROCESSING
------------------------

AADS is headquartered in Hong Kong. Our Users, service providers, and other third parties you may interact with in connection with our Services, may be located in different countries around the world, including countries that may not offer the same level of protection for Personal Information as that offered in Hong Kong. By accessing or using our Services in Hong Kong or any other country or jurisdiction, you agree that your information may be transferred and processed in Hong Kong and any other country or jurisdiction.

Our Services are not directed to anyone under 18, and we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from people in this age group. If you believe we may have collected Personal Information from anyone under the age of 18, please get in touch with us.

SECURITY
--------

Every AADS account is protected to help maintain privacy and security on our Services. If you register for an account, we urge you to use a strong password containing unique numbers, letters, and special characters and to protect the confidentiality of your password at all times. If you suspect or become aware of any unauthorized access to or use of your account or password, you agree to immediately notify us and change your password. We take reasonable technical and organizational measures to guard against unauthorized or unlawful processing of your personal data and accidental loss or destruction of, or damage to, your Personal Information. While no system is entirely secure, we believe the measures implemented by the site reduce our vulnerability to security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved. We have security measures to protect our user database, and access to this database is restricted internally. However, it remains your responsibility:

To protect against unauthorized access to your use of the site and/or Services;

To ensure no one else uses the Site and/or Services while your device is logged on to the site (including by logging on to your device through a mobile, Wi-Fi, or shared access connection you are using);

To log off or exit from the Site and/or Services when not using it;

Where relevant, keep your password or other access information secret. Your password and login details are personal to you and should not be given to anyone else or used to provide shared access, for example, over a network; and

To maintain excellent internet security.

It would be best if you kept all of your account details secure. If you think that any of your accounts have been compromised, you should change your account credentials with us, and in particular, make sure any compromised account does not allow access to your account with us. You should also tell us as soon as possible so we can try to help you keep your account secure and, if necessary, warn anyone else who could be affected.

Please note that while we seek to protect your information and maintain the security of our Services, due to the possibility of hardware or software failure, unauthorized entry or use, and other factors, we cannot guarantee the security of any information, whether online or offline. Any transmission of information is at your own risk. Please also note that any information you provide to us via e-mail is unencrypted.

STATUTORY REQUESTS
------------------

Some jurisdictions have laws that give people the right to access or correct the Personal Information which a company has about them. We will honour any statutory right you may have to access or correct your Personal Information in our records, and you can e-mail such requests via [https://aads.com/contact\_us](https://aads.com/contact_us). Once we receive your request, we will let you know if an administrative fee will apply to fulfil your request, as permitted by applicable law. However, please note that even if you have a legal right to request access to information or to correct information, as permitted by applicable law, we may reject unreasonably repetitive requests that would require disproportionate technical effort (for example, developing a new system or materially changing an existing practice), would jeopardise the privacy of others, or would be highly impractical to fulfil (for example, requests to access information located on backup systems).

DISPUTE RESOLUTION
------------------

As this Policy is part of our T&Cs, any disputes involving you and us that relate to privacy or the use of your information and that arise out of or are associated with this Policy or our Services will be subject to our T&Cs, including any provisions regarding the limitation of damages and liability, choice of law, and dispute resolution.

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
------------------------------

Our business changes with time, and our Privacy Policy will change also. We reserve the right to change this Policy, without prior notice, at any time at our sole discretion. For example, without limitation, we may change this Policy to reflect changes to the law or our Services. All changes to this Policy will be effective when posted on our Services or at a later date as may be specified in the updated Policy. We will notify you of any changes to this Policy by posting the updated Policy on our Services. You agree to review this Policy regularly and inform yourself of all applicable changes. By continuing to use our Services after any changes to this Policy become effective, you agree to such changes and the updated Policy. Unless we notify you otherwise, the current version of this Policy will apply to all information we have about you or your account.

COOKIE POLICY
-------------

Cookies, Web Beacons, Google ReCAPTCHA, and Similar Technologies: We may use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons, and similar technologies, such as tracking URLs, to collect information about how you or others access or engage with our Services, Content, e-mails, and ads displayed on or off our Services, and to operate, develop, improve, and customize our Services, Content, and marketing, including ads displayed on or off our Services. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but your browser may have settings that enable you to decline or delete cookies on your device. Please note that if you refuse cookies, you may not be able to sign in, customize, or use some of the interactive features of our Services, as some of our Services require cookies to operate.

What these Technologies Are: "Cookies" are small data files placed on your computer or other devices which record information. For example, a cookie could enable our Services to recognize your browser, while another cookie could store your account preferences and other information to help make our Services more customized. We may use two kinds of cookies, "session cookies" and "persistent cookies." Session cookies typically expire when you close your browser, while persistent cookies remain on your device until they expire or are deleted. "Web beacons' (also known as "pixel tags" or "clear GIFS") are pieces of code or pixels embedded in a web page or e-mail to track engagement with and responses to e-mails, web pages, or ads or to access or communicate with cookies. "Tracking URLs" are special URLs that can be used to track engagement with and responses to e-mails or web pages.

Third-Party Analytics, Service, and Ad Providers: We may use third-party analytics and services providers who help us better understand how our Services and Content are accessed and used, including for web analytics, audience measurement, personalization, segmentation, and relationship management purposes. In turn, this information helps us to develop and improve our Services and Content. Our third-party analytics and service providers include but are not limited to Google Analytics. These providers may use cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies to collect information about how Users access or engage with our Services, Content, e-mails, and ads on or off our Services. For more information about how Google may collect and process information in connection with Google Analytics and Google, click here.

We may also use third-party advertising providers, including ad networks or exchanges, to help display ads on our Services or other websites, including customized ads based on past online activity. These third parties may use cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies to help provide services to us and collect information about your and others' online activity across different websites. These providers may also collect your IP address, device identifier, or identifier for advertising (IDFA). The third-party advertising providers we use include but are not limited to Google Analytics. We use its Remarketing and Demographics and Interest Reporting features, which enable Google Analytics to collect data about the traffic on our Services through Google advertising cookies and anonymous identifiers. We and third-party providers, including Google reCAPTCHA and Google Analytics, may use first-party cookies (i.e., cookies set by the website you are visiting) and third-party cookies (i.e., cookies placed by a third-party website other than the website you are visiting) to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on past visits to our Services. We do not control the practices of any third-party providers. This Cookie Policy (and our Privacy Policy in general) does not cover using cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by any third parties.

Opting-Out: Third-party providers may offer a way to opt-out of receiving cookies from them by visiting their websites or the websites of industry groups such as the Network Advertising Initiative and the Digital Advertising Alliance. For example, you may opt out of receiving ad-related cookies from Google through its Ad Settings. If you opt out of receiving cookies from one of these providers, it may place a cookie on your device to remember your preference. Accordingly, if you delete cookies, install a new browser, or start using a new device, you may need to repeat the opt-out process. For more information about AdChoice, please visit their website. To opt out of receiving any marketing materials, please get in touch with us via [https://aads.com/contact\_us](https://aads.com/contact_us).

Changes to this Cookie Policy: As part of our Privacy Policy, we may update it at any time as described in our Privacy Policy. Please review this Cookie Policy regularly to be informed of any updates.

CONTACTING AADS
---------------

If you have questions or comments about our Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, or you would like to know what Personal Information we hold about you or would like to update, delete, or request access to such Personal Information, you may contact us via [https://aads.com/contact\_us](https://aads.com/contact_us). We will use commercially reasonable efforts to honor your request. We may retain an archived copy of your records as required by law or for legitimate business purposes, such as information stored in blockchain technology to verify the authenticity and value of digital assets. If you delete all your Personal Information, your AADS account may become deactivated.

You may access, correct, amend, or delete your User Materials by accessing your AADS account (including any imported contacts). You control all User Materials you upload. User Materials that you delete (including User Materials containing personal information) may be retained in archived or backup copies to enable you to use certain features like revision history and base snapshots. For instructions on permanently deleting User Materials from your account, please get in touch with us via [https://aads.com/contact\_us](https://aads.com/contact_us). Please note that permanent deletion of your User Materials through this process will impair or disable those features concerning that User Materials.

You may access, correct, amend, or delete the Personal Information we have about you by logging into your account and navigating your account page. If you wish to cancel your account, you may do so through your account page. If you do, personally identifiable information associated with your account will be deleted as soon as is reasonably practical or as required by applicable law. Please note that we may retain information that is otherwise deleted in anonymized and aggregated form, in archived or backup copies as needed under records retention obligations, or otherwise as required by law.

AADS Crypto Ad Network has been working with crypto and non-crypto websites since 2011, providing banner ad solutions. As a trusted Bitcoin advertising network, we prioritize delivering high quality crypto ads to increase the impact of your campaign. If you're looking to buy crypto traffic or attract visitors interested in cryptocurrencies, our service is ideal for you. Join our crypto advertising platform and discover the exceptional service we offer!

Advertising

Earning

Collaborations

Service

Company

We accept Bank Card

& Cryptocurrency payments

+16 more BNB, BTC, BCH, BUSD, DASH, DOGE, ETC, LTC, Polygon, SOL, SOLUSDT, TRX, USDC, USDT, USDT.TRC20, WAVES, WBNB, XEM, XRP, ZEC

Withdraw via [Lightning](https://a-ads.com/blog/effortlessly-withdraw-bitcoin-from-a-ads-using-lightning-network/)

 [English](javascript:void(0))

© AADS 2011-2024 [Terms of Service](https://a-ads.com/terms_of_service) [Privacy Policy](https://a-ads.com/privacy_policy)

Please enable JavaScript, disable ad blocking software and refresh the page.
